

KATA SERFŐZŐ

Visual Designer

PERSONAL DATA

- Ossastrasse 41, 12045, Berlin
- +49 15237778690
- ✓ kata.serfozo@gmail.com
- Be www.behance.net/kataserfozo
- nttps://kataserfozo.github.io

TOOLS OF CHOICE

Designing

Adobe XD Balsamique Sketch

Improving

AfterEffects Illustrator InDesign
Lightroom Photoshop

Cooperating

Figma InVision

Building

html, css

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Hungarian
English
Swedish
German

EXTRACURRICULAR

- 6 months in New Zealand on a working holiday scheme
- 3 months experience as a barista in London
- Volunteering for 3 months in Portugal in a surf camp
- Working as a freelance photographer and weddings
- Experience in Studio Photography

I'm a visual designer in love with UI design. I have a background in philology, finance, photography and graphic design. Due to my diverse professional experience I am able to adapt to different environments while adhering to professional integrity. Besides arts and creating, I love developing my skills, learning new tools and improving my design skillset, while making aesthetically pleasing and useful products and interfaces.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

01/2020- 04/2020 UI Designer Lendis, Berlin, Germany

- Collaborating with stakeholders over collecting requirements, creating user flows, wireframes and mockups for both customer facing applications and internal tools
- Collaborating with engineering department over executing the visual designs all the way from wireframes to final deliverables
- Establishing a company wide design system

09/2018- 04/2019 UI Design course CareerFoundry

- UI design for music, messaging, note-taking apps
- UX and UI design for cooking application for mobile and responsive design
- UI design for delivery application for iOS & Android Native app
- · UI design for money saving responsive website

10/2017 – 3/2018 Graphic and Web Design intern MediaSales, Budapest, Hungary

- · Creating banners, website and mobile interface design
- Creating images and ads for social media and presentations
- Designing products for print

04/2014 - 12/2016 Reporting Specialist
British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

- Employee database design, maintenance and reporting in business objects application
- Testing corporate data warehouse of the time, labour and project management tool

11/2013 – 03/2014 Finance Professional
British Telecom, Budapest, Hungary

Advising and solving issues of users of a project and people management system

EDUCATION

09/2018 - 04/2019 CareerFoundry, distance education
 UI Design

01/2010 - 06/2010 Rønde Højskole , Rønde, Denmark
 Arts, Project Management

09/2009 - 12/2013 Eötvös Loránd University, Budapest, Hungary BA, English and Scandinavian Studies